Okay,
what I was saying is it is showing a
limited set of line items, right?
If you remember,
in the direct shipment change,
Okay.
we had already listed a list of items,
fields that the user would want to see.
Correct?
The changes will be pushed to the top and
rest of the ones unchanged fields will
remain in the bottom, right?
So in this case,
the changed fields are showing,
but for the unchanged,
there are a lot more than just the two
fields.
Okay,
so you need the same for all all of the
all of the lines, right?
Correct.
It should exactly be the same as that of
the direct shipment, right?
In the direct shipment,
how many fields you have?
The same number of fields should be here
for the order change, right?
And we did talk about if the particular
order has multiple lines, right? Say,
for example, if you come down to...
Yeah.
volume, volume, volume is fine,
gross feed is fine, right?
But if you come down to something like a
line level item number,
item number has changed, right?
You're showing one item that has changed,
but it has the second line item,
which has not changed.
We are going to display that as well as
part of the item number.
So you want to display the ones that are
not changed as well.
Right.
Correct. If you go to direct shipments,
you have covered that.
If you close this one,
go to direct shipments.
This one.
Right, yeah, go to this is not direct.
Yeah, this is direct shipment. Yeah,
go to tender.
End the screen.
Right click on Review Order Change.
But if you come to the bottom.
Right, bottom or come down a little more,
yeah, click on this.
You'll see a lot more fields.
The preview tender details. Okay.
So you need the same thing there, right?
Right, right.
Right, right. Say in this case,
if you see marine equipment, right?
No.
Say for example, let's take one example.
Ship, not ship direction.
If you come down, hazmat code, right?
Hazmat code would be available for each
Yeah.
line item.
If there are two products within an order,
Touch.
right? Line one and line 2.
it might have UN 0324, right? 024.
Then it would have 0023 or 24 is being
repeated on the second line item as well.
If here you're showing just one line item,
but if there are more than one line item
on an order,
then you need to list all those as well.
Yeah.
Okay.
You're getting my point, right?
Mhm.
Yeah, see, yeah, so Flash,
similarly Flashpoint will have more if
Yeah, I understand.
the product has more,
if the product listing are more than one,
right?
It has two or more product listing within
the order.
Like that means that what I mean is line
numbers are more than one.
So you need to capture all those as line
number one, line number two.
to line #3,
and then within those you need to tell if
a particular item has changed,
this has changed.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Because every example is just showing one
field, but it won't be like that.
Some will be having more than one field,
right?
So that is why I'm saying wherever those
are multiple lines,
you need to show those multiple lines.
And all these are line level fields,
right? It is not, except for the gross.
But they are together, right?
Because these ones are like all of all of
the lines together, right?
Yeah, all of the lines together, correct.
The line level fields,
OK.
I think I have already mentioned it in
the story,
saying these are line level fields,
product level information,
these are header level information.
Maybe we can have something here visual,
right, to separate.
Yeah,
you can just put it inside the box saying
that line one and line 2, line one is yes,
line 2 is no. Yeah.
Separator here, yeah.
We just organize it in such a way that it
is differentiating between line one and
Okay.
line two, right? So line one, line two,
line three, if you have multiple lines,
just list them accordingly, right?
So that needs to be included in that.
That's one thing.
Let's go to the next one.
Okay, these ones are okay. One second.
Let me go through all this. This is fine.
Package count has changed.
These have changed. Yeah,
these looks okay. These are good.
Affected.
And you don't need affected in the
delivery because you need affected only
in the pickup.
Because everything that is going to be
picked up is going to be delivered, right?
You don't have to show the same thing,
the affected orders, right?
You don't have to show the same thing in
the,
what I'm saying is highlighting the
orders, right? Right side, right side.
Yeah.
Highlighting is fine, but right side,
right side you have the click,
click and open, right? Right side,
affected orders.
Yeah, this is this looks repeated, right?
You don't need it. Repeat it.
You don't need those.
Yeah,
you don't need the affected orders on the
again on the delivery, right?
That is what I'm saying.
Okay, okay, just one.
Yeah, just on the pickup level,
on the pickup you can have multiple
different orders on each of the pickup.
If you can show that only on the pickup
and just not to show them in the delivery,
that's fine. Affected orders, right?
I'm just talking about the second column.
Affected orders. In the affected orders,
you have the first box has, yeah,
you don't need that on the delivery
because that is already captured on the
first part.
Right, pick up.
Yep.
Right, OK, then once again,
view view planning dates,
view planning dates, you click on that,
do you see the planning date? Yeah,
that's fine. OK, yeah, that's fine.
Then if we close that one, please, yeah.
And view routing,
can you go to view routing? Okay,
this is going to show the new routing,
right?
Why this is showing a new routing is
because it's still a direct shipment.
Nothing has changed with related to stop
level information, correct?
Mm-hmm.
Right, if you can close this one,
I just wanted to see if there is any stop
information that has changed. Yeah,
stop has not changed.
So you have the location the same,
only the product information has changed.
No.
Yeah, that looks correct. Okay,
view routing,
so you have a new console cost. Okay,
I did notice that you are having...
Thank you.
difference in the cost here is 15 to 1.63,
right? But there on in the front page,
the rates are not correct.
The AP cost rates.
The new console cost is different.
You see that on the top, on the top.
Yeah.
You can no below new console cost,
new consolidation cost is there, right?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, it's different than here.
Yeah, it's different than here. Yeah,
it should be 15 to 1.63.
Go.
OK.
Right, so that is that's a small thing,
but I'm just saying if you want to make
Yes.
it consistent,
I did notice that in the direct shipment
as well.
Right? Okay, 15. Okay, this is good.
You're actually having JB hunt. Okay,
this is good. If you close this one.
Maybe they accepted we should put it on
top, right?
No, that is correct.
It will go according to the rank, right?
First got cancelled, second is declined,
the third one is accepted.
OK.
So the current one accepted is ABFS.
That's fine.
It is just that the box needs to be,
it should not be hidden,
it should be visible, right?
Maybe just focus on the accepted or the
current one, the last action.
In where?
No,
what I'm trying to say is if it is
accepted,
the last one action accepted or sent,
that should be the last.
Now the focus should be on that.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I was saying. Maybe,
maybe put the rank 3 here. I mean,
the order will be the same,
but I'm just saying let's put them this
in the beginning, right?
Scroll it, scroll it,
and put it on the top. OK.
But maybe,
maybe you know the second is accepted,
so it will always be here.
Yeah, I think that's fine.
It is understood.
People will scroll and they will be able
to find out, right? It's not a big deal.
Yeah.
But I would prefer to,
if this can open on a separate window,
And.
right,
if they can keep it on a separate window,
like right click and open it on a
separate window,
that will be really helpful.
instead of showing it just as pop-up
alone,
if they can open and keep it in the
second separate window,
because what happens is once they go into
the next page,
they would probably want to see the
routing information, right?
So it'll be really helpful for them to
view the keep the routing information
here and review it.
Yes.
Are you getting my point?
Yeah, trying to stand. Hey, let's go,
let's go with the next one.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, let's go into the, okay, edit ship.
Yeah, edit ship and stop.
Edit shipment.
Now this is fine. Earlier we talked about,
if you remember right,
we asked for the earlier plan to be
available on the left pane, right?
It is a compare screen.
But here we have only the new plan.
but they are not able to see the old plan.
Correct? See,
the old plan is on the previous page.
If you recall my mock that I gave you,
Right.
Yes.
right,
this and that were part of a single page.
And we discussed earlier saying that if
you could put a pane on the left,
which can slide left and right so that it
can go like between they can review the
old and what is the new. In this case,
it's very straightforward. It's okay,
but if it gets more complex,
then you have multi-stop shipments.
Let's go with the multi-stop.
I can not stop.
Oh.
I think the previous one was multi-stop,
yeah.
This one, this one is pretty big.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
So if you go here, right,
right now you're seeing only the new
version of it,
but you don't get the idea of what's the
old version, right?
That's why we said if you put a left pane
and the plane can close and open,
then you get the new view fixed.
But if they would want to reference the
old means prior.
View, you can still keep the prior view.
Makes sense.
Yeah, it makes sense. I understand that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, OK. OK, this one, uh,
it looks good if you, if you go up,
if you go up a little bit.
Okay, this one prior, new. Okay,
new consolidation here you don't have
because something has changed related to,
if you can go back, if you can go back,
I just wanted to see what location had
changed.
Right, in this one, the first location.
Okay, Houston has changed. Okay,
so it is not going to be Houston,
it is going to be something else. Okay,
so now Miami, Florida, Minneapolis.
Okay, then, like Houston,
you have Houston, one other order,
Thank you.
and delivery is going to happen.
In to.
If you come down,
how many deliveries are there?
Four and five? Yeah, four and five. Okay.
One, two, three, no,
it's just one delivery, 2 deliveries,
Yeah, 2 deliveries. Yeah,
four and five is going to be delivery.
and one, two, three pickups.
Three pickups,
3 pickups and four deliveries. Okay,
so now in order to move these up and down,
you can move it up and down, right?
Yes.
So you can just move. That is fine.
That functionality is good.
Okay.
And move to pending.
Why do you have to move to pending?
Yeah.
Oh, for each order. Okay, for each order,
you're having a move to pending, right?
Okay.
And you can add it to somewhere.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I will come to that functionality.
You cannot add it to somewhere, right?
You can add it to only to that location.
Say you don't give the option to add it
to stop 2 or stop 3 because it already
Yes, exactly.
has a location.
So it can go if it is already an existing
location. Say for example,
If 947, what is it,
94740 is a Minneapolis,
Call.
you cannot choose it to add it to stop
three.
It should go and add it only to stop two.
Makes sense.
Um, but the stop three is is pickup.
Why not that in here? Ah,
because the does they don't match the
place, right?
Correct. You can add to a different place.
That is why you should not give that
functionality there, saying that,
you know, go and add to the stop.
All that you can say is remove it and add
it. System will decide where to add it,
but you can then readjust it accordingly,
right? If it is an existing stop.
Yep.
It will go and add it to Minneapolis.
For example, if the removed order,
if you remove 94740,
can you just remove the 94740 and stop 2?
Move to pending.
This one, right?
Yeah, yeah, remove that. OK,
now select this and move it to stop one.
Right?
This is going to be wrong because you're
moving it from Minneapolis stop to
Florida stop, which is completely wrong.
This order cannot be picked there.
Yeah, OK.
Right?
That is why I'm saying you should not
give that functionality.
All that you can say is add or remove.
That's all.
Pen.
Right? Instead of saying move to pending,
do you want to say remove?
Just keep it as remove.
I don't know what terminology or word I
gave. I think I said remove and add.
Simple.
Right, if you can.
Because remove feels like it's going to
be removed,
but move depending will be here, right?
You are not removing anything because
removing means disappear from everywhere.
Yeah, that is delete, right?
We are not deleting anything.
Say remove is remove from the particular
stop. That's what it means.
I don't know. I mean, to me,
it feels very weird because remove is
almost the same as delete.
Okay, let's keep it removed to pending.
Yeah, okay, let's leave it as it is. Okay,
And.
but I'm saying it's a longer word, right?
So it is like kind of long and how do you
Okay.
say it's occupying a lot of space.
That's why I was thinking that just
Okay.
remove would be better, but that's fine.
Let's leave it.
I'll change, I'll look for another one.
Yeah, okay, so if you remove it,
it should go there. When a user adds it,
it automatically should add it to the
right location.
Do you want to?
That's what the logic should be, right?
If it is a...
Okay.
So here I don't have the choice to add
some more that I think,
because I was thinking maybe we should
type everyone else that is not Miami,
let's say for example.
Just give me one second.
You don't have to do it, right?
System is already going to do it.
So you just give option to add it.
So it goes and adds to that particular
stop, right?
Automatically moves it to that stop and
moves it to the right delivery location.
If that delivery location does not exist,
Thank you.
it is going to create a new delivery
location.
Right, and...
And then why do you have the need to,
if the system is going to decide,
why do you have the need to?
To move it manually.
Yeah, how do you change it?
Say for example,
You don't need it.
if I want to pick Minneapolis 1st and
Miami later, I can do it.
The user can decide.
Let's say this is Miami, right?
Right.
So,
if the system will decide where this is
going.
Which I think it will put it here,
then why I have the the option to move it
Right.
or to delete it from here?
It can be that process can be also do
Yeah, it is a...
done automatically when I when I go here,
right?
By system.
When I when I when I land in this page,
system will already design it.
That's it.
You don't need to do it this anymore.
Yeah, but how do you want to rearrange?
System has already decided.
This is how you need to pick up.
There is no choice.
This is avoid error from the user side,
right?
If you give this option and if you let
the user to decide,
they might plug the wrong order into a
wrong stop. We don't want that.
That's what I'm saying. You don't need it.
You don't need to decide anymore, Ben.
Right,
that is the reason why we are saying
don't decide it.
The only option the user will have is
switch between 2 pickups.
I want to do pickup 2 first right now
instead of pickup one, right?
That is what they can decide.
The.
The only place then you're saying the
only place where I can decide is in this
place, right?
Let's say here I have 4 orders.
In between those four,
I can decide which one goes first, right?
Not for goes first,
which which one I want to keep,
which I which one I want to remove, say,
for example.
Ah, okay, which one I want to keep,
which one I got,
because you can take it out of here and
then just approve it and that's it.
Yeah.
That's it. Yeah, right. So that.
You are just removing this one. Okay.
And then you can change their order as
well.
Yeah, you can change the order.
Say you can move stop 2 to stop one and
Okay.
stop one to stop 2.
Yeah, I know the stops,
but can you change the order of, oh,
they don't have, they don't have, yeah,
because this is a stop, right?
No, no, no, they...
That means all of the orders will be
picked up here, right? Okay, okay, okay.
Correct.
Here, correct. Exactly.
It is going to go to one particular
location from, it's going,
truck is going to go to a location and
going to pick up everything in one shot.
Okay.
Right, OK,
so one other thing that is missing is
And.
distance between P1 and P2, right?
It should start calculating the distance
between P1 and P2.
Between P1 and P2. OK,
maybe show somewhere the distance, right?
P1 and P2, right?
Yeah,
there you need to show the distance and
P2 to P3 and P3 to P4 and D1, D2,
all that intermediate stops you need to
But.
show distance, right?
And maybe the total here,
all these things.
Yeah, total is already covered on the top,
right? You have it on the top, I believe.
Ohh yeah, right, you're right. OK,
Windows Phone.
Yeah.
So you just need to break it down so that
they know as they keep changing these
stops, right, adjusting. Say, for example,
if they move from stop 2 to stop one,
say stop,
they move stop 2 to stop one and stop one
to stop 2,
maybe the distance has changed, right?
It's no more consistent or they move stop
Bing.
Thank you.
3 in between stop 2, maybe the distance,
the overall distance has changed.
System is going to recalculate it.
And.
Right?
So it gives the user idea of saying,
are they making the right decision
between stops? Right? Is it nearby?
Hey, hold up.
Where is it? Right? All those things.
Yeah.
Okay, that you need to add. Okay,
this one. Okay, if you go back,
I go see.
rest of the ones looks good.
Delivery date.
How do they add the delivery date?
A pickup date?
The.
How do they change the pickup date?
How do we change the pickup date?
Right,
they should be able to change the pickup
date in each of the stops.
Don't have that from Laura. Okay. No,
I don't.
Give me one second, maybe here.
Do that one.
It should be here, yeah.
No, this is not the one. Yeah,
this is the stop level change. Yeah.
No, I don't. No, I don't have it.
I don't have it.
So it should be inside this one where the
user will be able to change the pickup
stop, right? Stop one.
Stop one is a pickup stop.
So I should be able to change from 14th
January to 19th January.
Right, I should be able to.
And then the system will recalculate the
other file.
Right,
and what happens is when it changes,
if you go to the planning table, right?
Say, for example,
if you go to the view planning table,
right? Right,
you have what is the order on stop one?
If you go to stop one,
what is the order on stop one? Right,
you have two orders, right? 4, 7,
37 and 39. Okay,
Thirty-seven.
go back to the planning table.
37 and 39. Okay, just focus on 37, right?
It says what date, 14th January?
14th January is the pickup, right?
If you change to 19th January on the stop
No.
level, on the stop information,
you have a pickup date, correct?
Okay.
If you change it to 19th January,
the earliest is 14th and the latest is
And.
15th.
14th.
So this should be highlighted saying that,
okay,
now you've changed this top level pickup
date to 19th and now you're not meeting
the constraints passed on on the order.
Make sense?
No.
Does it make sense, Manuela? Right,
because you would want to pick up the
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
order between these two dates.
The earliest you can pick up is 14th and
the latest you can pick up is 14th.
Here in this case, it's 8 A.m. and 1 P.m.
Between 8 and 1 P.m. you can pick up,
right? Say for example,
Pizza.
I'm not meeting that.
I'm going to change on the stop level
to pick up on 19th,
then it is going to throw or make a color
on this particular order planning dates,
earliest pickup and latest pickup,
saying that I have not met the planning
dates as expected on the order.
So I'm not picking up on 14th,
I'm picking up on 19th on a different
Under.
date.
So those two are going to be highlighted.
No.
Similarly, it is applicable for delivery.
If you have delivery dates and those
Okay.
delivery dates are not being met,
but the user will be able to change those
on the multi-stop or consolidations,
then those will be highlighted to the
user saying that your plan.
So,
highlighted means means you need to edit
them as well, right?
No,
you should be able to edit only on this
top level.
This is highlighted on the planning dates.
Planning dates comes from the order.
Okay.
Right, order should not be touched.
30 yard.
Dunk.
This is the reference.
This is what the customer sent us,
but we are not able to meet it,
but we are planning it in a different
date,
but the planner should know that you are
planning it on a different date.
I am aware about it, right?
That's why the system is trying to tell
them.
Yeah.
Right, if you close this one,
what the user will do is,
if you come down to the stop one,
stop one, you see the date pickup date,
right?
That is the date that they will be
Play.
editing, right?
They can change it from 14th to 19th or
Right.
20th.
Right, you need to have an edit of date,
time, date, time, what is that, month,
Are you?
Typically.
date, day, and time, right?
All those fields should be editable.
Okay.
You don't need delivery date, right?
I don't know distance.
Distance should be moved to the left.
Right, between P1 and P2U2,
you should have the distance, or you can,
if you want to populate there,
that's also fine, right?
Okay.
Yeah, we don't have,
we don't need this here.
Yeah, if you want to put it to the side,
that looks even better, right? Yeah.
For pickup, you should have pickup date.
For delivery,
you should have delivery date.
You don't need delivery date here on this
one, right? Right in the stop one.
You don't need the delivery date.
You just need the pickup date. For every.
And they cannot be the same, right?
Because this is the second pickup.
This is different.
Yeah, they can be the same.
They can be the same, right,
provided the user looks at it and
evaluates it, right? Say, for example,
ideally, if I go to pick up in Miami,
I cannot pick up the same day in
Minneapolis.
Those are really far off places. But
If I live in Miami, Florida,
in this particular zip code,
and my stop 2 is in Miami, Florida,
it's an adjacent zip code, right?
Ohh yeah.
I would be able to pick up on the same
date, right?
These are the ones that the planner will
have to go and adjust, right?
What am I?
They will look at it and say, okay,
the distance between P2 and P3
Right, P1 and P2 is a hot 1000 miles.
I cannot do the delivery date pickup date
on 14th,
so it should be ideally something else.
Make sense?
Yes.
Okay, okay.
So we don't need delivery date on a
Yes.
pickup stop. We need only a pickup date.
Similarly, on a delivery stop,
we don't need a pickup date.
So that needs to be changed.
Okay, so the other ones looks good.
You need to add the prior plan onto the
Go.
left, that one. Okay, if you can add,
if you can remove an order from stop two,
right, let it go to pending.
OK, now let's add a new order.
Okay, new order,
the user will be only vouchers, correct?
OK.
You should be able to filter only by
vouchers and...
You think about this?
Yeah,
and is there a filtering option here?
Sharon.
Okay, you have filtering option. Okay,
so order number, by shipment, shipment ID,
destination, fantastic.
And do you have by shipment status you
have? Okay, 10 to 7. Very good, that's it.
You filter by any of these and you should
I wanna fix that one.
be able to select an order and add, right?
The only thing is, it should not,
it shouldn't prevent the user from,
I believe.
Before you should be able to simulate and
add it,
any order you should be able to add it,
right?
I could not remember what rule I wrote.
You should be able to add any order,
but while confirming,
if it is already tender sent,
it should not allow the user to finalize
it.
It should tell them a message saying that
the current...
order is tender sent,
you need to cancel the tender before you
can add the order to this one, right?
That's the only requirement. Yeah,
It should work.
if you can add anything apart from tender
sent, right? Just add something.
And.
Play.
Add an order that is from Florida, right?
Maybe this one?
Yeah, San Diego, yeah, okay, added.
Okay,
to this order came in and now you add
this order, VAL10.
Yeah, just click on.
The system would decide, but we,
at this point, I don't know how it works,
right?
When you click on add, yeah,
when you click on add and that particular
Since then, so.
location is not part of the existing
location, it will add us a new stop.
And that new stop will be P question mark.
But I don't see that, right?
Here it says.
When you add that,
you should change it into P question mark.
Okay, so yeah,
that needs like you're creating a new
stock or something for it.
Yeah, a new stop is created,
but it is not finalizing that stop.
It is putting it as question mark,
P question mark,
because it has a new pickup. Say,
for example, that is a San Diego pickup,
right? So San Diego is not here.
So it should add a pickup stop as a P
question mark, because it's a pickup stop,
but you don't know what number the user
is going to pick.
fix it at, right?
So it will put it as P question mark and
wait for the user to select and move it.
Similarly,
if the delivery is also not part of the
existing delivery,
it will put a D question mark and wait
for the user to finalize it.
Right, that thing needs to be added.
In this particular case,
if you directly add it,
it is going to go into a stop.
It should not go, say,
if it is an existing stop,
it should attach to a stop.
But if it is completely a new stop,
it should allow the user,
it would create a new stop,
mark it as P question mark,
and then wait for the user to do it.
Similarly.
the case when an order has undergone,
existing order has undergone a location
change. If it underwent a location change,
it should not create a location.
It should create a location,
but put it as a question mark for the
user to move the order into a right
location.
The same concept works while adding an
order.
while also order undergoing a change
location change and entering into the
screen.
Makes sense.
Yes.
Right, okay.
No.
So yeah, that is the part that is missing.
Once that question mark is created, right,
then the user will move it into a
particular stop and then it'll get a
location, automatically get a spot for it,
right? It'll be either P2 or P3, right,
or P1. Wherever they are moving,
it's going to get a location number for
it.
Open, Sinha.
I don't.
And I'm open.
So, when this will happen?
What do you mean when this will happen?
Approve changes, because I did some.
Approve changes will happen once
everything is finalized, right?
There is no question mark,
there is no P question mark,
everything looks okay,
then approve changes.
That's when the user,
you have to call the routing, right?
There is another option there.
The user should be able to call the
routing once they have.
made all these changes. Where is that one?
No, I don't know. Laura did this,
so I'm trying to...
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, those changes are there.
So they have to run the routing list
again, right, and see the routing.
Right, what?
Ohh, we don't have that.
Yeah, let me see.
Do you have my design that I sent you
earlier?
Probably, I need to double-check, Janice.
I don't.
Okay, you make these changes, right?
Again,
we will connect tomorrow and maybe I will
send you the latest one. Yeah,
Okay, and we can follow up on that.
we'll follow up on that because once you
make those changes,
what should happen is the user should be
able to call the routing and be able to
see the list, routing list.
If you go up,
you should probably have some list there.
Yeah, sorry.
Right, if you go up, please,
on that one that you are sharing.
Right, view planning dates, view routing.
See, once they finalize it,
I think once they save,
they should be able to see the routing,
view routing.
Once you, once you save the plan,
once you close this,
Good morning.
not the planning dates,
you close this one.
No.
There you go.
Yeah, save, make the approved changes,
make the approved change.
Like, I cannot, it's blocked.
I don't know why.
Okay, so once you approve changes,
then you should be able to see the
I have to check.
routing list, view routing list.
OK, you're outing this, OK.
So that is complete or no?
And again, yeah.
I don't know.
I think to me it looks complete well.
I still need to fix this part.
Yeah, you need to fix that one.
We need to finalize the plan.
Once you finalize the plan,
system should call the routing and get
the fetch the route list.
Yeah, now it's fixed,
but this now happens.
No, possibly.
Yeah, now it is generating. You see that?
It's the new list and the old list.
Thank you.
So the user will be able to see the new
list and the old list.
And once they see the new list,
view routing, right,
it should take them to the planning
screen, right? If you remember,
we had a planning screen, right?
OK, no,
I don't have a planning screen here.
Yeah,
it should go to the planning screen and
then it should take them to the
finalization,
just like how we have for direct, right?
You want to use, you want to send the,
what is that?
You want to bypass tender or accept
tender, right?
So those options should come.
So those are the other ones that are
missing here.
Okay.
I'll send you the latest one that I sent
to Laura or whoever I have sent it to,
right?
Just take a look at it and then we will
connect again tomorrow.
Okay,
I don't know if I can have all of those
changes tomorrow.
I still need to work on other stuff.
Sure, yeah, yeah, okay, okay, yeah.
Maybe some of them that we can connect.
Okay, yeah, yeah, sure. Thank you. Bye.
See you later. Thank you. Bye bye.
Yeah, talk to you later, bye.